[{"answer": " Hi", "docId": "319tiny.htm.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Um, y'know, before we go ah, there's something I need to say", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "...so y'know, that's why, within a few years, that voice recognition is gonna be pretty much standard on any computer you buy.  Y'know, so you could be lik", "docId": "319tiny.htm.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Yeah, it was", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I mean I think I'd say no to anybody right now.   Oh, but it was so strange.  I mean I'm standing there with this charming, cute guy, who's asking me to go out with him, which I'm allowed to do, and I felt guilty.  Y'know, like I'd be cheating on my friend or something", "docId": "319tiny.htm.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I don't have any issues with my Father", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yeah, ", "docId": "319tiny.htm.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "It's still a gift!  I got it from the gift shop", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Oh, you are a petty man.  You are a petty, petty...", "docId": "319tiny.htm.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Petty...", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Petty..", "docId": "319tiny.htm.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Petty..", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Petty...", "docId": "319tiny.htm.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Petty..", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Petty..", "docId": "319tiny.htm.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Petty..", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Petty..", "docId": "319tiny.htm.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Small...", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "my friend!  You gotta stop!  Okay?!  You can't just stare through the peep hole for three hours!  You're gonna get peep eye", "docId": "319tiny.htm.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You didn't just break up", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "And the inventor of the door rests happily in his grave", "docId": "319tiny.htm.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Stop what?", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "She's moving on!  Okay, if it's not this guy, it's gonna be somebody else!  And unless you're thinking about subletting my peep hole, you are going to have to get used to the fact that the relationship is over!  Okay, man?  It's over", "docId": "319tiny.htm.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Okay", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Y'know what", "docId": "319tiny.htm.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I can't do this", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "No.  And I don't think I'm gonna want to", "docId": "319tiny.htm.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Yep.  Yep, that's what I didn't want to know", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Yep.  Yep, that's what I didn't want to know", "docId": "319tiny.htm.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Ahh!  Fair, schmair!  Y'know?  Look, if you want to get back at my friend, I am here for you.  Really?  N", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "It isn't", "docId": "319tiny.htm.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Oh, okay.  There should be Gold Man", "qsentId": 32}]